&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：关于未定义与未声明的快速说明。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: A quick note on undefined versus undeclared.
这通常是令人困惑的。
This is often confused.
这是令人困惑的，因为开发者，很自然地，
And it's confused because developers, quite naturally,
把这些词看作是一种同义词。
think of these words as sort of synonyms.
看起来他们的意思几乎是一样的。
They seem like they mean kind of almost the same thing.
在英语中，这可能是真的。
And in English, that's probably true.
但在编程中，这完全不是真的。
But in programming, it's entirely not true.
在编程中，特别是在JavaScript中，
In programming, and especially in JavaScript,
这是两个完全不同的概念。
these are two entirely different concepts.
所以在上一张幻灯片上，当我说V型的时候，我得到了引用，
So on the previous slide, when I said type of V, and I got back quote,
UNDEFINED，V或其他变量，甚至不存在。
undefined, V or whatever that variable is, didn't even exist.
所以，当有些东西甚至没有定义的时候，我怎么才能拿回未定义的报价呢？
So how is it that I can get back quote undefined when something doesn't even
存在吗？
exist?
好吧，这是另一个历史性的疣，JavaScript试图假装
Well, that's another historical wart, JavaScript trying to pretend as if
没有声明也没什么大不了的。
the absence of a declaration isn't that big a deal.
这不是什么大问题，你可以解决它。
It's not that big of a problem, you can work around it.
回想起来，他们根本就不应该这么做。
In retrospect, they never should have done that.
它们应该只是返回一个未声明的字符串。
They should have just returned a string undeclared.
未声明意味着它从未在我们有权访问的任何作用域中创建。
Undeclared means it's never been created in any scope that we have access to.
而未定义意味着肯定有一个变量，而目前，
And undefined means there's definitely a variable, and at the moment,
它没有价值。
it has no value.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：非常不同的事情。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Very different things.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：运算符的类型是存在的唯一运算符
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: The type of operator is the only operator in existence
它能够引用不存在的东西，并且不会抛出错误。
that is able to reference a thing that doesn't exist and not throw an error.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：现在，未定义和
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Now, undefined and
在未声明的情况下，我们可以相当直截了当地筛选出来。
undeclared, we can fairly straightforwardly sift those out.
但是在引入的语言中还有另一个空虚的概念，
But there's another concept of emptiness in the language that was introduced with,
本质上，ES6。
essentially, ES6.
描述这一点的最好方式是未初始化。
And the best way to describe this is uninitialized.
另一种方式来指代这个特殊的
Another way of referring to this particular
变量可以处于的条件称为TDZ，即时间死区。
condition that a variable can be in is called the TDZ, the temporal dead zone.
在我们讨论的下一个单元中，我们将会对此进行更多的讨论
We're gonna get much more into this in our next unit of discussion when we talk
关于范围。
about scopes.
我们要谈谈这东西是从哪里来的。
We're gonna talk about where this thing comes from.
但本质上，这个想法是某些变量，比如块范围的变量，
But essentially, the idea is that certain variables, like block scope ones,
不要初始化。
don't get initialized.
它们从来不会最初设置为undefined。
They never initially get set to undefined.
当某物处于未初始化状态时，它是禁止的。
When something is in an uninitialized state, it is off-limits.
你不允许以任何方式触摸它，形状或形式，否则你会得到一个错误，并且
You're not allowed to touch it in any way, shape or form, or you'll get an error, and
您得到的错误是TDZ错误。
the error you get is the TDZ error.
所以这是我们对这种空虚的另一个概念。
So it's yet another concept that we have of this emptiness.
我们可以有一个从未初始化的变量。
We can have a variable that's never been initialized.
我们可以有一个已初始化的未定义的变量。
We can have a variable that's been initialized that is undefined.
或者我们可以有一个从未创建过的变量，然后它是未声明的。
Or we can have a variable that was never even created, and then it's undeclared.
三个不同的概念，我们需要我们的大脑围绕着这三个不同的概念。
Three different concepts that we need to wrap our brains around.